{
    "NumberSystem":[
        {"id":1,"question":"A composite number is a natural number.","A":"TRUE","B":"FALSE","C":"Partially True","D":"Partially False","ans":"A","detail":""},
        {"id":2,"question":"A fraction in which the denominator is 10, 100, 1000, and so on is called a ____________.","A":"Proper fraction","B":"Decimal fraction","C":"Improper fraction","D":"None of the above","ans":"B","detail":"2.456 = 2456/1000"},
        {"id":3,"question":"A fraction representing the combination of _____ and ___________ is called an improper fraction.","A":"A numerator, a denominator","B":"A whole, a part of whole","C":"A & B","D":"None of the above","ans":"B","detail":"A whole(1) + a portion(1/4) is called improper fraction."},
        {"id":4,"question":"A fraction that represents _________ is called a proper fraction.","A":"A part of the whole","B":"More than one","C":"Less than one","D":"A complete whole","ans":"A","detail":"The result of a proper fraction is always less than one."},
        {"id":5,"question":"A natural number that has exactly 2 factors is called ___________.","A":"Prime number","B":"Composite number","C":"Co-prime number","D":"Rational number","ans":"A","detail":"The prime number 7 has only 1 & 7 as its factors."},
        {"id":6,"question":"A number that has more than 2 factors is called ______________.","A":"Prime number","B":"Composite number","C":"Co-prime number","D":"Rational number","ans":"B","detail":"The composite number 4 has 1, 4 & 2 as its factors."},
        {"id":7,"question":"A positive number has _____ square roots.","A":"One","B":"two","C":"Three","D":"A & B","ans":"B","detail":"The number 36 has two square roots. √36 = √(+6)x(+6) = 6 OR √36 = √(-6)x(-6) = -6"},
        {"id":8,"question":"A rational number has _______ equivalent rational numbers.","A":"Infinite","B":"Only one","C":"No","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"1/4 is the same as 2/8, 3/12, 4/16, …"},
        {"id":9,"question":"A square root of a number is a value; when the value is multiplied by itself gives that number.","A":"TRUE","B":"FALSE","C":"True or False","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"√9 is equal to 3 and when 3 is multiplied by itself gives that number 9"},
        {"id":10,"question":"All integers, all fractions, all decimal numbers that can be written as p/q (q≠0) are called _______.","A":"A rational number","B":"An ir-rational number","C":"Mixed fraction","D":"Improper fraction","ans":"A","detail":"1/0 is not defined."},
        {"id":11,"question":"All natural numbers are _____________fractions.","A":"Proper","B":"Improper","C":"Proper or improper","D":"None of the above","ans":"B","detail":"Any natural number can be written as improper fraction. 1/1, 2/1, 3/1, 4/1, …...  . But 0/1 is a proper fraction."},
        {"id":12,"question":"All-natural numbers greater than 1 have at least_____ factor/factors.","A":"One","B":"Two","C":"Three","D":"One & two","ans":"B","detail":"Any natural number other than 1 has at least 2 factors (1 & the number itself)"},
        {"id":13,"question":"An irrational number is some decimals ________________.","A":"Not terminating","B":"Not repeating","C":"Repeating & not terminating","D":"A & B","ans":"D","detail":"Irrational numbers are real numbers but they are not rational numbers, because irrational numbers neither terminates nor repeats"},
        {"id":14,"question":"Any positive rational number is greater than ____________.","A":"One","B":"Any negative rational number","C":"Zero","D":"B & C","ans":"D","detail":"Zero is neither a positive nor a negative rational number."},
        {"id":15,"question":"Any rational number can be represented as___________.","A":"Terminating decimals","B":"Non repeating decimals","C":"Repeating decimals","D":"A & C","ans":"D","detail":"Terminating and repeating decimals are rational numbers."},
        {"id":16,"question":"Convert 0.3333… to a fraction.","A":"1/5","B":"1/3","C":"1/7","D":"1/6","ans":"B","detail":"0.3333… can be written as 0 .3̅. Assume x = 0.3̅, then 10x = 3.3̅. Solve 10x - x = 3.3̅ - 0.3̅ => 9x = 3 => x = 3/9 = 1/3."},
        {"id":17,"question":"Convert 2.373737… to a fraction.","A":"155/99","B":"230/99","C":"235/99","D":"245/99","ans":"C","detail":"2.373737… can be written as 2 .3̅7̅. Assume x = 2.3̅7̅, then 100x = 237.3̅7̅. Solve 100x - x = 237.3̅7̅ - 2.3̅7̅ => 99x = 235 => x = 235/99."},
        {"id":18,"question":"Convert 4.568756875687…. to a fraction","A":"45683/9999","B":"45687/9999","C":"45686/9999","D":"45685/9999","ans":"A","detail":"4.56875687… can be written as 4 .5̅6̅8̅7̅. Assume x = 4.5̅6̅8̅7̅, then 10000x = 45687.5̅6̅8̅7̅. Solve 10000x - x = 45687.5̅6̅8̅7̅ - 4.5̅6̅8̅7̅ => 9999x = 45683 => x = 45683/9999."},
        {"id":19,"question":"Define HCF","A":"Find all factors of each number & Multiply them.","B":"Find all factors of each number & Multiply only the common between them.","C":"Find all multiples of each number & Multiply them.","D":"Find all multiples of each number & Multiply only the common between them.","ans":"B","detail": "Factors of 12 & 18 are (2, 2, 3) & (2, 3, 3). The common factors are 2 & 3. And the HCF is 2x3 = 6."},
        {"id":20,"question":"Define LCM","A":"Find all factors of each number & Multiply them.","B":"Find all factors of each number & Multiply only the common between them.","C":"Find all multiples of each number & Multiply them.","D":"Find all multiples of each number & Multiply only the common between them.","ans":"C","detail":"Multiples of 12 & 18 are (2, 2, 3) & (2, 3, 3). Combined multiples are 2, 2, 3, 3. And the LCM is 2x2x3x3 = 36."},
        {"id":21,"question":"For any three integer p, q, and r, p x (q + r) = (p x q) + (p x r) is called the distributive property of integer under multiplication","A":"Closure property  of integer under multiplication","B":"Distributive property  of integer under multiplication","C":"Additive identity  of integer under multiplication","D":"Multiplicative identity of integer under multiplication.","ans":"D","detail":""},
        {"id":22,"question":"For any three integers p, q, and r, then (p x q) x r= p x ( q x r)is called ___________________________.","A":"Closure property  of integer under multiplication","B":"Associative property  of integer under multiplication","C":"Additive identity  of integer under multiplication","D":"Commutative property  of integer under multiplication","ans":"B","detail":""},
        {"id":23,"question":"For any three integers p, q, and r, then (p+q)+r= p+ ( q+r)is called the associative property of integer under addition.","A":"Closure property  of integer under addition","B":"Associative property  of integer under addition","C":"Additive identity  of integer under addition","D":"Commutative property  of integer under addition","ans":"B","detail":""},
        {"id":24,"question":"For two integers p and q, then p x q = q x p is called _________________________.","A":"Closure property  of integer under multiplication","B":"Associative property  of integer under multiplication","C":"Additive identity  of integer under multiplication","D":"Commutative property  of integer under multiplication","ans":"D","detail":""},
        {"id":25,"question":"For two integers p and q, then p+q = q+p is called _____________________.","A":"Closure property  of integer under addition","B":"Associative property  of integer under addition","C":"Additive identity  of integer under addition","D":"Commutative property  of integer under addition","ans":"D","detail":""},
        {"id":26,"question":"If a & b are real numbers, then √(a/b) = _________.","A":"√(a+b)","B":"√(a-b)","C":"√a / √b","D":"√a * √b","ans":"C","detail":"√(36 / 4) = √(9) =  3 and the same is true as √(36 / 4) = √36 / √4 = 6 * 2 = 3"},
        {"id":27,"question":"If a & b are real numbers, then √(ab) = ________.","A":"√(a+b)","B":"√(a-b)","C":"√a / √b","D":"√a * √b","ans":"D","detail":"√(9 * 4) = √(36) =  6 and the same is true as √(9 * 4) = √9 * √4 = 3 * 2 = 6"},
        {"id":28,"question":"In 2345.657, what is the place for number 7?","A":"1000th place of decimal value","B":"1000th place","C":"A & B","D":"1/1000th place","ans":"D","detail":""},
        {"id":29,"question":"In a proper fraction, the numerator is ________ than the denominator.","A":"Less","B":"More","C":"More or less","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":""},
        {"id":30,"question":"In an improper fraction, the numerator is __________ or equal to the denominator.","A":"Less","B":"More","C":"More or less","D":"None of the above","ans":"B","detail":""},
        {"id":31,"question":"On a number line, when we add a negative integer to a given, then the result is to the _______ of the given number.","A":"Left","B":"Middle","C":"End","D":"Right","ans":"A","detail":"When adding the negative integer of -5 to any number(+ of -5 is a subtraction), it will move on to the left of the number line."},
        {"id":32,"question":"On a number line, when we add a positive integer to a given, then the result is to the _________ of the given number.","A":"Left","B":"Middle","C":"End","D":"Right","ans":"D","detail":"When we add the positive integer of 5 to any number, it will move on to the right of the number line."},
        {"id":33,"question":"On a number line, when we subtract a negative integer to a given, then the result is to the_________of the given number.","A":"Left","B":"Middle","C":"End","D":"Right","ans":"D","detail":"When subtracting the negative integer of -5 to any number(- of -5  is an addition of +5), it will move on to the right of the number line."},
        {"id":34,"question":"On a number line, when we subtract a positive integer to a given, then the result is to the________of the given number.","A":"Left","B":"Middle","C":"End","D":"Right","ans":"A","detail":"When subtracting the positive integer of 5 to any number, it will move on to the left of the number line."},
        {"id":35,"question":"Other names of co-prime numbers are ___________________.","A":"Relatively prime","B":"Mutually prime","C":"A&B","D":"None","ans":"C","detail":""},
        {"id":36,"question":"Repeating decimal is a decimal in which ___________ repeating indefinitely.","A":"One digit or a block of digits are","B":"One digit is","C":"A block of digits are","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"1.33333... & 1.21212121… are repeating decimals"},
        {"id":37,"question":"Represent the rational number -3/2 on a number line.","A":"Falls between -2 & -3","B":"Falls between -1 & 0","C":"Falls between -1 & -2","D":"Falls between -3 & -4","ans":"C","detail":"-3/2 = -1.5, which falls between -1 & -2."},
        {"id":38,"question":"The division is _______________ for integers","A":"Not commutative","B":"Commutative","C":"A & B","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"(p ÷ q) ≠ (q ÷ p)"},
        {"id":39,"question":"The division is__________ operation of ______________.","A":"Inverse, addition","B":"Inverse, multiplication","C":"Repeated, addition","D":"Inverse, subtraction","ans":"B","detail":""},
        {"id":40,"question":"The product of a number and its reciprocal is one, which is called the ________________.","A":"Divisibility of fraction","B":"Multiplicative fraction","C":"Multiplicative inverse of a fraction","D":"None of the above","ans":"C","detail":"2*1/2 = 1"},
        {"id":41,"question":"The product of a positive integer and a negative is ___________________.","A":"A positive integer","B":"A negative integer","C":"A positive or negative integer","D":"None of the above","ans":"B","detail":"2 * -3 = -6"},
        {"id":42,"question":"The product of an even number of negative integers is _________________.","A":"A positive integer","B":"A negative integer","C":"A positive or negative integer","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"-2 * -3 * -4  * -5 = 120"},
        {"id":43,"question":"The product of an odd number of negative integers is ________________.","A":"A positive integer","B":"A negative integer","C":"A positive or negative integer","D":"None of the above","ans":"B","detail":"-2 * -3 * -4 = -24"},
        {"id":44,"question":"The product of any number of positive integers is ___________________.","A":"A positive integer","B":"A negative integer","C":"A positive or negative integer","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"2 * 3 = 6"},
        {"id":45,"question":"The product of three negative integers is ________________.","A":"A positive integer","B":"A negative integer","C":"A positive or negative integer","D":"None of the above","ans":"B","detail":"-2 * -3 * -4 = -24"},
        {"id":46,"question":"The product of two improper fractions is greater than each of the two fractions.","A":"TRUE","B":"FALSE","C":"True or False","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":""},
        {"id":47,"question":"The product of two improper fractions is more than one.","A":"TRUE","B":"FALSE","C":"True or False","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":""},
        {"id":48,"question":"The product of two negative integers is _______________.","A":"A positive integer","B":"A negative integer","C":"A positive or negative integer","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"-2 * -3 = 6"},
        {"id":49,"question":"The product of two positive integers is _____________.","A":"A positive integer","B":"A negative integer","C":"A positive or negative integer","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"2 * 3 = 6"},
        {"id":50,"question":"The product of two proper fractions is less than _______.","A":"One","B":"Zero","C":"two","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"1/2 * 1/2 = 1/4, which is always less than one for any proper fraction"},
        {"id":51,"question":"The product of two proper fractions is less than each of the two fractions.","A":"TRUE","B":"FALSE","C":"True or False","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":""},
        {"id":52,"question":"The square root of a negative number is _________.","A":"Not a real number","B":"A real number","C":"A rational number","D":"A irrational number","ans":"A","detail":"The numbers which can not be represented using integers, fractions & decimals are not real numbers. Example √(-3) & (2+3i)"},
        {"id":53,"question":"The sum of a positive & a negative integer is _____________.","A":"Negative","B":"Positive","C":"Positive OR Negative","D":"None of the above","ans":"C","detail":"2 + (-3) = 2-3 = -1 (a negative number) & 4+(-2) = 4-2 = 2 (A positive number). "},
        {"id":54,"question":"The sum of two negative integers is __________.","A":"Negative","B":"Positive","C":"Positive OR Negative","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"-2 + (-3) = -2-3 = -5"},
        {"id":55,"question":"The sum of two positive integers is__________.","A":"Negative","B":"Positive","C":"Positive OR Negative","D":"None of the above","ans":"B","detail":"2+3 =5"},
        {"id":56,"question":"Two numbers that have only one common factor, and it is 1, are called __________.","A":"Prime number","B":"Composite number","C":"Co-prime number","D":"Rational number","ans":"C","detail":"The prime numbers 2 & 3 OR 11 & 19 are having 1 as a common factor between them."},
        {"id":57,"question":"We can insert Infinite rational numbers between any two rational numbers.","A":"TRUE","B":"FALSE","C":"True or False","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"Between 1 & 2, we can have an infinite number of rational numbers like 1/1000, 2/1000, …. & 1/10000, 2/10000,…. & …."},
        {"id":58,"question":"We can represent ________ as a proper fraction.","A":"One","B":"1/4","C":"1/2","D":"Zero","ans":"D","detail":"For example, zero can be represented as 0/7."},
        {"id":59,"question":"We get an equivalent rational number when we multiply the numerator and denominator by the same number, provided________.","A":"The multiplying number is not zero","B":"The multiplying number is not One","C":"The multiplying number is neither One nor zero","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"When 1/3 is multiplied by 0 on both numerator, and denominator we get 0/0, which is not defined."},
        {"id":60,"question":"What are Integers?","A":"1,2,3,4,…","B":"0,1,2,3,4,…","C":"...,-3,-2,-1,0,1,2,3,…","D":"1/4,1/2,3/4,1,1 1/4,…","ans":"C","detail":"All numbers including positive and negative numbers are called Integers"},
        {"id":61,"question":"What are natural numbers?","A":"1,2,3,4,…","B":"0,1,2,3,4,…","C":"...,-3,-2,-1,0,1,2,3,…","D":"1/4,1/2,3/4,1,1 1/4,…","ans":"A","detail":"All numbers used for counting are natural numbers"},
        {"id":62,"question":"What are non-terminating decimals?","A":"They have repeating decimals","B":"They are rational numbers","C":"They are irrational numbers","D":"A, B, & C","ans":"D","detail":"Non-terminating number are both rational & irrational numbers. Neither terminating & nor repeating decimals are irrational numbers. Terminating & repeating decimals are Rational numbers."},
        {"id":63,"question":"What are real numbers?","A":"Rational numbers","B":"Irrational numbers","C":"Integers","D":"A & B","ans":"D","detail":"Real numbers include rational & irrational numbers."},
        {"id":64,"question":"What are whole numbers?","A":"1,2,3,4,…","B":"0,1,2,3,4,…","C":"...,-3,-2,-1,0,1,2,3,…","D":"1/4,1/2,3/4,1,1 1/4,…","ans":"B","detail":"Zero & all natural numbers are whole numbers"},
        {"id":65,"question":"What is a terminating decimal?","A":"It has finite number of decimals","B":"It has no decimals","C":"It has repeating decimals","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"3/2 = 1.5 is a terminating decimal."},
        {"id":66,"question":"What is the difference between rational numbers and fractions? ","A":"Rational numbers can have natural numbers & fractions can have only whole numbers","B":"Rational numbers can have fractions & fractions can have only whole numbers","C":"Rational numbers can have integers & fractions can have only whole numbers","D":"None of the above","ans":"C","detail":"Fractions can not have negative numbers. And rational numbers can have negative numbers."},
        {"id":67,"question":"When a and b are ________ and ______, then a/b is called a rational number.","A":"Natural Numbers, b ≠ 0","B":"Whole Numbers, b ≠ 0","C":"Integers, b ≠ 0","D":"None of the above","ans":"C","detail":"1/0 is not defined, and -3/5, 0/1, 1/2 are rational numbers"},
        {"id":68,"question":"When a and b are whole numbers and __________, the a/b is called a fraction.","A":"b ≠ 1","B":"a ≠ 0","C":"b ≠ 0","D":"a ≠ 1","ans":"C","detail":"a/0 is not defined, but when b ≠ 0, then 0/b is the proper fraction"},
        {"id":69,"question":"When a decimal number is divided by 10, 100, 1000, and so on or any higher power of 10, then the decimal point is shifted to the left by n places, where n is ________.","A":"The number of digits after decimals","B":"The number of digits before decimals","C":"The number of zero","D":"None of the above","ans":"C","detail":"243.67 is divided by 100, and we get 2.4367, in which the decimal is moved by 2 digits left because 100 has 2 zeros."},
        {"id":70,"question":"When a decimal number is multiplied by 10, 100, 1000, and so on or any higher power of 10, then the decimal point is shifted to the right by n places, where n is _____________.","A":"The number of digits after decimals","B":"The number of digits before decimals","C":"The number of zero","D":"None of the above","ans":"C","detail":"2.4367 is multiplied by 100, and we get 243.67, in which the decimal is moved by 2 digits right because 100 has 2 zeros."},
        {"id":71,"question":"When a number is multiplied by itself, then the product is the square of that number.","A":"TRUE","B":"FALSE","C":"True or False","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"3*3 = 9 which is 3²"},
        {"id":72,"question":"When a point indicates the ___________ in the numerator, then the expression is called decimal.","A":"Quotient","B":"Denominator","C":"Reminder","D":"None of the above","ans":"B","detail":"In 25.26358 the value represented after the point (.26358) indicates the denominator of that decimal fraction."},
        {"id":73,"question":"When a, b and c are natural numbers and ab = c, then a and b are ______ of c.","A":"Multiples","B":"Factors","C":"Quotients","D":"Reminders","ans":"B","detail":"Example: 2 x 3 = 6 then 2 and 3 are factors of 6. 6 is multiple of ‘2’ as well as ‘3’."},
        {"id":74,"question":"When the product of two non-zero numbers is one, then each of these is the __________ of others.","A":"Duplicate","B":"Reciprocal","C":"Negative","D":"None of the above","ans":"B","detail":"2 * 1/2 = 1"},
        {"id":75,"question":"When the sum of two integers is zero, each integer is said to be the ______________ inverse of the other.","A":"Associative","B":"Commutative","C":"Closure","D":"Additive","ans":"D","detail":"2 + (-2) = 0; Additive inverse of 2 is -2."},
        {"id":76,"question":"When we add two integers, their sum is also an integer is called ____________________.","A":"Closure property  of integer under addition","B":"Associative property  of integer under addition","C":"Additive identity  of integer under addition","D":"Commutative property  of integer under addition","ans":"A","detail":""},
        {"id":77,"question":"When we add zero to an integer, we will get the same integer is called the additive identity of integer under addition.","A":"Closure property  of integer under addition","B":"Associative property  of integer under addition","C":"Additive identity  of integer under addition","D":"Commutative property  of integer under addition","ans":"C","detail":""},
        {"id":78,"question":"When we divide a negative integer by a negative integer, we get ___________.","A":"A positive integer","B":"A negative integer","C":"A positive or negative integer","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"-4 /-2 = 2"},
        {"id":79,"question":"When we divide a negative integer by a positive integer, we get ____________________.","A":"A positive integer","B":"A negative integer","C":"A positive or negative integer","D":"None of the above","ans":"B","detail":"-4/2 = -2"},
        {"id":80,"question":"When we divide a positive integer by a negative integer, we get _________.","A":"A positive integer","B":"A negative integer","C":"A positive or negative integer","D":"None of the above","ans":"B","detail":"4/-2 = -2"},
        {"id":81,"question":"When we divide a positive integer by another positive integer, we get ________________.","A":"A positive integer","B":"A negative integer","C":"A positive or negative integer","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"4/2 = 2"},
        {"id":82,"question":"When we divide an integer by 1, we get the __________.","A":"Another integer","B":"Same integer","C":"One","D":"Zero","ans":"B","detail":""},
        {"id":83,"question":"When we multiply 1 to an integer, we will get the same integer is called _________________________.","A":"Closure property  of integer under multiplication","B":"Associative property  of integer under multiplication","C":"Additive identity  of integer under multiplication","D":"Multiplicative identity of integer under multiplication.","ans":"D","detail":""},
        {"id":84,"question":"When we multiply an improper fraction with a proper fraction, the result is ______ than the proper fraction and _______ than the improper fraction.","A":"Less, greater","B":"Less, less","C":"Greater, Less","D":"Greater, greater","ans":"C","detail":"3/2 * 1/2 = 3/4 in which 3/4 > 1/2 & 3/4<3/2"},
        {"id":85,"question":"When we multiply two integers, their product is also an integer is called____________________.","A":"Closure property  of integer under multiplication","B":"Associative property  of integer under multiplication","C":"Additive identity  of integer under multiplication","D":"Commutative property  of integer under multiplication","ans":"A","detail":""},
        {"id":86,"question":"When we want to divide a fraction by a whole number, we multiply the fraction by the ________________________.","A":"Multiplicative inverse of the whole number","B":"Whole number","C":"One","D":"A & C","ans":"A","detail":"1/2 ÷ 4 = 1/2 * 1/4 "},
        {"id":87,"question":"When we want to divide a fraction by another fraction, we multiply the first fraction with the _____________.","A":"Reciprocal of the second fraction","B":"Second fraction and inverse the result","C":"Second fraction","D":"Reciprocal of the second fraction and inverse the result","ans":"A","detail":"1/2 ÷ 1/4 = 1/2 * 4/1"},
        {"id":88,"question":"When we want to divide a whole number by a fraction, we multiply the whole number by the ___________.","A":"Fraction and inverse the result","B":"Fraction","C":"Reciprocal of the fraction and inverse the result","D":"Reciprocal of the fraction","ans":"D","detail":"4 ÷ 1/2 = 4 * 2/1"},
        {"id":89,"question":"When we write an improper fraction as an integer, followed by a proper fraction is called ____________.","A":"Integer","B":"Proper fraction","C":"Improper fraction","D":"Mixed Fraction","ans":"D","detail":"1 followed by 2/3 is written as 1 2/3, which called mixed fraction."},
        {"id":90,"question":"Which is greater?","A":11.45,"B":11.38,"C":11.4,"D":11.42,"ans":"A","detail":""},
        {"id":91,"question":"Which is greater?","A":10.1,"B":10.01,"C":10.001,"D":10.08,"ans":"A","detail":""},
        {"id":92,"question":"Zero is greater than any negative rational number.","A":"TRUE","B":"FALSE","C":"True or False","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"Zero is neither a positive nor a negative rational number."},
        {"id":93,"question":"Zero is less than any positive rational number.","A":"TRUE","B":"FALSE","C":"True or False","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"Zero is neither a positive nor a negative rational number."},
        {"id":94,"question":"∏ is an irrational number.","A":"TRUE","B":"FALSE","C":"True or False","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"∏ = Pi = 3⋅14159265… which is neither repeating nor terminating and it is an irrational number"},
        {"id":95,"question":"√(3) = ?","A":1.414,"B":1.732,"C":2.236,"D":2.449,"ans":"B","detail":"1.732 * 1.732 = 2.999824 which is close to 3"},
        {"id":96,"question":"√(5) = ?","A":1.414,"B":1.732,"C":2.236,"D":2.449,"ans":"C","detail":"2.236 * 2.236 = 4.999696 which is close to 5"},
        {"id":97,"question":"√(6) = ?","A":1.414,"B":1.732,"C":2.236,"D":2.449,"ans":"D","detail":"2.449 * 2.449 = 5.997601 which is close to 6"},
        {"id":98,"question":"√2 is an irrational number. ","A":"TRUE","B":"FALSE","C":"True or False","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"√2 = 1.41421356237309504…. which is neither repeating nor terminating and it is an irrational number"},
        {"id":99,"question":"√3 is an irrational number. ","A":"TRUE","B":"FALSE","C":"True or False","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"√3 = 1.732050807…. which is neither repeating nor terminating and it is an irrational number"},
        {"id":100,"question":"∛8 = ?","A":1,"B":2,"C":3,"D":4,"ans":"B","detail":"∛8 = ∛(2x2x2 ) = 2"},
        {"id":101,"question":"0 ÷ 0 is _________.","A":0,"B":1,"C":"Not defined","D":"None of the above","ans":"C","detail":"Any number divided by 0 is not defined."},
        {"id":102,"question":"0/1 is a fraction. True or False. (True)","A":"TRUE","B":"FALSE","C":"True or False","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"0/1 is a proper fraction"},
        {"id":103,"question":"0/1 is a rational number. True or False.","A":"TRUE","B":"FALSE","C":"True or False","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"0/1 is a proper fraction, and it can also be said as a rational number."},
        {"id":104,"question":"1 ÷ 0 is ________.","A":0,"B":1,"C":"Not defined","D":"None of the above","ans":"C","detail":"Any number divided by 0 is not defined."},
        {"id":105,"question":"1/0 is a fraction. True or False.","A":"TRUE","B":"FALSE","C":"True or False","D":"None of the above","ans":"B","detail":"Any number divided by 0 is not defined."},
        {"id":106,"question":"1/0 is a rational number. True or False. (False)","A":"TRUE","B":"FALSE","C":"True or False","D":"None of the above","ans":"B","detail":"Any number divided by 0 is not defined."},
        {"id":107,"question":"1+2/3 = 1 2/3.","A":"TRUE","B":"FALSE","C":"True or False","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"1 + 2/3 = 5/3 & 1 2/3 can be written as 5/3"},
        {"id":108,"question":"10/10 is an improper fraction.","A":"TRUE","B":"FALSE","C":"True or False","D":"None of the above","ans":"A","detail":"Because any number more than or equal to one can be written as improper fraction."},
        {"id":109,"question":"4 has ____ square roots, and _______.","A":"One, it is 2","B":"Two, they are +2 & -2","C":"A & B","D":"None of the above","ans":"B","detail":"The number 4 has two square roots. √4 = √(+2)x(+2) = 2 OR √4 = √(-2)x(-2) = -2"},
        {"id":110,"question":"-5 ½ is neither an integer nor a fraction, and it is _________.","A":"A rational number","B":"An ir-rational number","C":"Mixed fraction","D":"Improper fraction","ans":"A","detail":"All negative fractions are rational numbers"}
    ]
}